🎵 Way Maker (길을 만드시는 분) - 찬양 전주
Way Maker - Leeland (Intro)
[1절] 이곳에 운행하시는 주님, 주를 예배합니다
You are here, moving in our midst; I worship You
주를 예배합니다
I worship You
이곳에 역사하시는 주님, 주를 찬양합니다
You are here, working in this place; I worship You
주를 찬양합니다
I worship You
[1절 반복] 이곳에 임재하시는 주님, 주를 경배합니다
You are here, moving in our midst; I worship You
주를 예배합니다
I worship You
이곳에 일하시는 하나님, 주를 찬양합니다
You are here, working in this place; I worship You
주를 찬양합니다
I worship You
[후렴] 길을 만드시는 분, 기적의 주, 약속을 지키시는 분
You are Way maker, miracle worker, promise keeper
어둠 속의 빛, 나의 하나님, 그분은 나의 주님
Light in the darkness, my God, that is who You are
[후렴 반복] 길을 만드시는 분, 기적의 주, 언약의 하나님
Way maker, miracle worker, promise keeper
어둠 속의 빛, 나의 하나님, 그분은 나의 주님
Light in the darkness, my God, that is who You are
[2절] 상한 마음 만지시는 주님, 주를 예배합니다
You are here, touching every heart; I worship You
주를 예배합니다
I worship You
모든 아픔 고치시는 주님, 주를 찬양합니다
You are here, healing every heart; I worship You
주를 예배합니다
I worship You
모든 삶을 변화시키는 주님, 주를 예배합니다
You are here, turning lives around; I worship You
주를 찬양합니다
I worship You
부서진 맘 싸매시는 주님, 주를 경배합니다
You are here, mending every heart; I worship You
주를 예배합니다
I worship You
[후렴] 길을 만드시는 분, 기적의 하나님, 약속을 지키시는 분
Way maker, miracle worker, promise keeper
어둠 속의 빛, 나의 하나님, 그분은 나의 주님
Light in the darkness, my God, that is who You are
[후렴 반복] 길을 만드시는 주, 기적의 하나님, 나의 구원자
Way maker, miracle worker, promise keeper
어둠 속의 빛, 나의 하나님, 신실하신 나의 주
Light in the darkness, my God, that is who You are
[선포] 그분은 나의 하나님, 신실하신 나의 주!
That is who You are! That is who You are!
길을 만드시는 주, 나의 하나님, 살아계신 나의 주님
That is who You are, Jesus, that is who You are
[브릿지] 보이지 않아도 주 일하시네
Even when I don't see it, You're working
느껴지지 않아도 역사하시네
Even when I don't feel it, You're working
결코 멈추지 않으시네
You never stop, You never stop working
주님은 결코 멈추지 않으시네
보이지 않아도 주 일하시며, 느껴지지 않아도 역사하시네
Even when I don't see it, You're working; Even when I don't feel it, You're working
결코 멈추지 않으시네, 주님은 결코 멈추지 않으시네!
You never stop, You never stop working! You never stop!
[브릿지 절정] 결코 멈추지 않으시는 나의 하나님! 길을 만드시는 분!
You never stop working! Way maker, miracle worker!
[후렴 절정] 길을 만드시는 분, 기적의 하나님, 어둠 속의 빛!
Way maker, miracle worker, promise keeper, Light in the darkness!
모든 이름 위에 뛰어난 주 예수 그리스도!
His Name is above every name, Jesus Christ!
살아계신 나의 주, 영원한 나의 하나님을 찬양합니다
That is who You are, that is who You are!
🕊️ 길을 만드시는 신실하신 주님을 영원히 찬양합니다 · 아멘
Giving Praise to the Way Maker, Our Faithful God · Amen